Arjay Castro Angeles

Address: 1249 Sta. Barbara, Baliuag, Bulacan

Email: rjayangeles@yahoo.com Phone: +63 905 549 1147



SUMMARY

Current Customer Advocacy Manager. Versatile, reliable and efficient with over 8 years of professional experience in the field of Digital Advertising. Diversified skills include in-depth knowledge in Rich Media Ads Development, Email Development, Campaign Management, Technical Support, Troubleshooting/Debugging, Customer Services, SAAS, JIRA, Salesforce, DoubleClick Studio API, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Google Web Designer.

CERTIFICATION

DOUBLECLICK STUDIO BADGES





GOOGLE WEB DESIGNER BADGE



WORK EXPERIENCE

MAPP DIGITAL

CUSTOMER ADVOCACY MANAGER

(SEPTEMBER 2019 – MARCH 2020)

- Management and follow-up of front-line customer service and technical support tickets for company inquiries, contract and renewal questions, and Mapp Cloud solutions on an international level
- Basic and complex analysis of technical support requests

- Interface with Engineering Team on P1 or complex issues, including ticket submission for customer and ensuring handling/resolution occurs
- Maintain and achieve customer and internal SLAs
- o Build a sustainable and mutually beneficial relationship between customers and Mapp

CAMPAIGN MANAGER

(JULY 2018 – AUGUST 2019)

- Coordinate, facilitate & manage day-to-day tasks involved in deploying global omnichannel campaigns
- Testing and editing / amending HTML email codes
- Complete quality assurance checks on all campaigns. Ensuring best practice is met at all times
- Manage, integrate and modify/update subscribers
- Deploy emails to appropriate subscriber audiences
- Proactively make suggestions to improve campaign performance
- Liaise with clients in order to relay any information, or solve queries
- Ensure campaign requests are accurately and efficiently fulfilled within agreed timescales

COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS PHILIPPINES INC.

CREATIVE ADS SUPPORT SPECIALIST 2 - vGuru (SEPTEMBER 2017 – JUNE 2018)

- Perform the same tasks with creative ads support specialist.
- Receive level 2 escalations from support agents and provide instruction and insights how to resolve the issue.
- Test and verify any report platform bugs and issues to Engineering team.
- Monitor and assist other support agents on their chat sessions and email tickets to ensure that the team provides the best support and client experience.
- Create root cause analysis on customer feedback and formulate measures to minimize dissatisfied customers.
- Review, monitor, and resolve pending tickets in the Creative Ads Support queue using the process knowledge and product expertise to achieve the team standard SLA's (service level agreement).
- Help our Team Leads by providing insights/feedback to get high customer satisfaction rating for the team.

CREATIVE ADS SUPPORT SPECIALIST (DECEMBER 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2017)

- Provide support via chat and email channel to Studio advertisers, creative agencies and individual clients with questions about HTML5 banners, Google Web Designer and DoubleClick Studio.
- Apply advanced troubleshooting techniques and resolves technical issues on creatives built in plain HTML5 and Google Web Designer.

- Learn new trends in building creatives including HTML5, CSS and Javascript to cope up
 with the recent changes in the Rich Media and Digital Advertising Industry.
- Provide assistance on inquiries regarding various Rich Media formats such us in-page banners, expanding, interstitial/floating, lightbox, masthead and VPAID.
- Provide templates and guide clients through implementation of DoubleClick components and custom solutions.
- Monitor task queue, delivery status, and take measures to ensure productivity.
- o Contribute in the documentation of bugs and their fixes shared to the team.
- Initiate updates on DoubleClick Help Center articles.

BACKEND CREATIVE DEVELOPER (SEPTEMBER 2014 - DECEMBER 2015)

- Normalizing unreleased products built by the Innovation Services team to ensure quality and readiness for external usage.
- Produce and develop creative template based Flash or HTML5 content from supplied assets based on market needs; manage <u>template database</u> to be kept up to date with current product versions.
- Improve the product as a whole through participation in usability testing and bug outs.
- Create and update technical client facing documentation on current products; manage
 Custom Layout templates in DoubleClick Studio as needed.
- Manage template database to be kept up to date with current product versions.
- Create/update technical client facing documentation on current products.
- Monitor task queue, delivery status, and take measures to ensure productivity.

SENIOR POST PRODUCTION DEVELOPER (MARCH 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014)

- Develop Rich Media ads using DoubleClick Studio; worked with diverse Flash and HTML5 creatives and apply the site-specific specification.
- Create dynamic creatives to increase creative development efficiency using various targeting rules.
- Ensure cross-browser compatibility and resolve bugs when it's possible.
- Communicate with Rich Media Specialists and Campaign Managers about the task at hand clarifications and requests, through verbal, chat, or e-mail.
- Take in charge of the Team whenever Rich Media Specialist/Team Leads are unavailable/out of the office.
- Help train new developers through shadowing system and motivates them to do their best.
- Perform pre-QA testing of creatives before sending to Quality Assurance team; create notes concerning the tasks for Quality Assurance Specialist's reference.
- Ensure that the creatives are properly pushed/trafficked to the adserver DoubleClick Campaign Manager (DCM).
- Develop templates that can be used to speed up production.
- Monitor delivery status and slack time and takes measures to ensure productivity.

WIDE-OUT WORKFORCES INC.

RICH MEDIA DEVELOPER

(JUNE 2011 - MARCH 2014)

- Develops Rich Media ads using DoubleClick studio; worked with diverse Flash and HTML5 creatives, mainly Youtube mastheads and apply the site-specific specification.
- o Debug/Troubleshoot rich media creatives.
- Perform pre-QA testing creatives before sending to Quality Assurance team; create notes concerning the tasks for Quality Assurance Specialist's reference.
- Communicates with Rich Media Specialists and Campaign Managers about the task at hand clarifications and requests, through verbal, chat, or e-mail.
- Learn new production design, development methodologies, trade tools and apply them in production.
- Help train new developers through shadowing system and motivates them to do their best.
- Take in charge of the Team whenever Rich Media Specialist/Team Leads are unavailable/out of the office.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE MAJOR IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

BALIUAG UNIVERSITY

2007 - 2011